in the last video you saw what a single
在上一期的视频中我们已经见过
hidden layer neural network looks like
只有一个隐含层的神经网络
in this video let's go through the
在这期的视频中让我们了解
details of exactly how this neural
神经网络的输出
network computers outputs
究竟是如何计算出来的
what you see is that is like logistic regression
你所看到的是像逻辑回归（那样的运算过程）
but repeat of all the times
但整个运算过程会重复很多遍
let's take a look so this is what's a two layer neural network
看一下 这是一个两层的神经网络
let's go more deeply into exactly what
让我们更深入地了解到底
this neural network compute
神经网络是怎么计算的
now was said before that logistic regression the circle images（感觉这里英文错了）
这是我们之前提及的逻辑回归 用圆圈表示
the regression really represents two steps of computation
这个回归代表了计算的两个步骤
first you compute Z as follows
首先你按步骤计算出Z
and in second you compute the activation as a sigmoid function of Z
然后在第二步中你以sigmoid函数为激活函数计算Z（得出a）
so a neural network just does this a lot more times
所以一个神经网络只是这样子做了好多次
let's start by focusing on just one of the nodes in the hidden layer
让我们从关注隐含层的第一个神经元开始
and this look at the first node in the hidden layer
看看这个隐含层的第一个神经元
so I've grayed out the other nodes for now
我暂时先隐去其他的神经元
so similar to logistic regression on the left
左边看上去和逻辑回归很相似
this node in a hidden layer does two steps of computation
隐含层的这个神经元进行两步计算
right the first step we think it's as the left half of this node
第一步 我们认为神经元的左半边
it computes Z equals W transpose X plus B
计算z = wTx + b
and the notation we'll use is um these
这些我们会用到的标记
are all quantities associated with the first hidden layer
都与第一隐含层数量相关
so that's why we have a bunch of square brackets there
所以这就是我们为什么在那用了一组方括号
and this is the first node in the hidden layer
这是隐含层的第一个神经元
so that's why we have the subscript one over there
所以这就是为什么我们有一个下标1在那
so first it does that
第一步就是这样
and then a second step is it computes
然后第二步是计算
a11 equals sigmoid of z11 like so
a[1]1 = sigmoid(z[1]1) 就像这样
so for both Z and a the
所以对于z和a
notational convention is that a Li the L
按惯例记号是a[l]i
here in superscript square brackets refers to layer number
这里上标方括号表示层数
and the i subscript here refers to the nodes in that layer
而下标i则表示层中的第几个神经元
so then we will be looking at is layer 1 that is a hidden layer
然后接下来我们看这是第一层 即隐含层
node 1 so that's why the superscript and
它的第一个神经元 这就是为什么上标和
subscript were on both 1 1
和下标都是1 1
so that little circle that first node in neural network
所以这个小圆圈 即神经网络的第一个神经元
represents carrying out these two steps of computation
表示着执行计算的两个步骤
now let's look at the second node in neural network the
现在让我们看看神经网络的第二个神经元
second node in the hidden layer of in neural network
即神经网络中隐含层的第二个神经元
similar to the logistic regression unit on the left
与左边的逻辑回归单元类似
this little circle represents two steps of computation
这个小圆圈代表了计算的两个步骤
the first step is compute Z
第一步是计算Z
this is still layer 1 but now the second node
这还是在第一层 但是是第二个神经元
equals W transpose X plus B
= wT x + b
and then a 12 equals Sigma z12 and
然后a[1]2 = sigmoid(z[1]2)
again feel free to pause the video if you want
再次 你可以选择暂停视频如果你想
but you can double check that the superscript and subscript notation
这样你就可以再次查看标记的上标和下标
is consistent with what we have written here above in purple
和我们上面所写的是保持一致的
so we've talk through the first two hidden units
所以我们已经讨论了隐含层的前两个神经元
in the neural network on hidden units three and four
在神经网络中 第三四个
also represents some computations
也是表示同样的计算
so now let me take this pair of equations
现在让我们把这对等式
and this pair of equations
还有这对等式
and let's copy them to the next slide
把他们复制到下一个幻灯片中
so here's our network and
这是我们的神经网络
here's the first and there's a second equations
这是第一个等式 这是第二个等式
they were worked on previously for the first and the second hidden units
他们之前已经在隐含层的第一二个神经元中被计算过了
if you then go through and write out the corresponding equations
如果你接下去看并且写出相应的等式
for the third and fourth hidden units
对应于第三 第四个隐含层单元
you get the following
你就会得到下面的这些（等式）
and let's make sure this notation is clear
让我们确认下这个记号
this is the vector W 11 this is a vector transpose x ok
这是向量w[1]1 这个向量的转置 x
so that's what the superscript T there
那上面的上标T
represents this is a vector transpose
表示这是一个向量的转置
now as you might have guessed
现在就像你可能所猜想的那样
if you're actually implementing in neural network
如果你确实在神经网络中执行
doing this with a for loop seems really inefficient
用for循环来做这些看起来真的很低效
so what we're going to do is
所以接下来我们要做的就是
take these four equations and vectorize
把这四个等式向量化
so I'm going to start by showing how to compute Z as a vector
我将从展示如何把Z当做一个向量计算开始
it turns out you could do it as follows
结果显示 你可以按接下来的（方法）做
let me take these WS and stack them into a matrix
让我们把这些w们堆积起来形成一个矩阵
then you have W 1 1 transpose
然后你就有w[1]1转置
so that say a row vector oh that's a column vector transpose
所以这是这个行向量（口误） 这是一个列向量的转置
gives you a row vector
变为一个行向量
then W 1 2 transpose W 1 3 transpose and W 1 4 transpose
然后 w[1]2转置 w[1]3转置以及w[1]4的转置
and so this by stacking those four W vectors together
把这四个w向量堆积在一起
you end up with a matrix
你会得出一个矩阵
so another way to think of this is that
另一个看待这个的方法是
we have for logistic regression unions there
我们有四个逻辑回归单元
and each of the logistic regression unions
且每一个逻辑回归单元
have a corresponding parameter vector W
都有相对应的参数 向量w
and by stacking those four vectors together
把这四个向量堆积在一起
you end up with this four by three matrix
你会得出这个4 × 3 的矩阵
so if you then take this matrix and
然后如果你把这个矩阵
multiply it by your input features x1 x2 x3 you end up with
乘以你的输入 特征 x1 x2 x3 你会得出
by our matrix multiplication works you end up with
从我们的矩阵乘法中你会得出
W11 transpose x W21 transpose X of W31 transpose X W41 transpose X
w[1]1转置x w[1]2转置x w[1]3转置x w[1]4转置x
and then let's not forget the bs
然后别忘记了b们
so we now add to this a vector
让我们现在加上一个向量
b[1]1 b[1]2 b[1]3 b[1]4 so that they see this
b[1]1 b[1]2 b[1]3 b[1]4 所以他们看起来这样
then this is b[1]1 b[1]2 b[1]3 b[1]4
然后 b[1]1 b[1]2 b[1]3 b[1]4
and so you see that each of the four rows of this outcome
然后你会看到这四行的结果
correspond exactly to each of these four rows
恰好对应于这四行（口误）
of each these four quantities that we had above
对应于上面的这四个等式
so in other words we've just shown that
换句话说 我们刚刚展示了
this thing is therefore equal to Z11 Z12 Z13 Z14
这个东西是等于z[1]1 z[1]2 z[1]3 z[1]4
right as defined here
就如之前在这定义的
and maybe not surprisingly we're going to
这可能并不奇怪 我们将
call this whole thing the vector Z1
把这整个东西称作向量Z[1]
which is taken by stacking up these um individuals of z
Z[1]是通过堆积这些单独的z
into a column vector
放进一个列向量中
when we're vectorizing one of the rules of thumb
当我们向量化时一条经验法则
that might help you navigate
可能帮助你找到方向
this is that when we have different nodes in a layer
就是当我们在一层中有不同的神经元
we stack them vertically
那就纵向地堆积他们
so that's why when you have Z11 to Z14
这就是为什么当你有Z[1]1~Z[1]4
those correspond to four different nodes in the hidden layer
对应隐含层4个不同的神经元
and so we stack these four numbers vertically to form the vectors Z1
我们把这四个数纵向堆积以形成向量Z[1]
and to use one more piece of notation（英文错了，翻译是猜的）
再说下这个标记
this 4 by 3 matrix here which we obtained by
这个4×3的矩阵是我们通过
stacking the lower case you know W11 W12 and so on
堆积小写的你懂的 w[1]1 w[1]2 等等 形成的
we're going to call this matrix W capital 1
我们将称呼这个矩阵为大写的W[1]
and similarly this vector we going to call B superscript 1 square bracket
类似的这个矩阵被称为B上标[1]
and so this is a 4 by 1 vector
所以这是个4×1的向量
so now we've computed Z using this vector matrix notation
所以现在我们计算Z通过运用向量或矩阵标记
the last thing we need to do is also compute these values of a
最后一件需要做的事是计算这些a的值
and so probably won't surprise you to see that we're going to define a1
所以你应该不会惊讶 我们要把a[1]定义为
as just stacking together those activation values a11 to a14
a[1]1~a[1]4这些激活后的值的堆积
so just take these 4 values and stack them together in a vector called a1
所以把这四个值堆积在一个向量里就形成a[1]
and this is going to be sigmoid of z1
这里就会有sigmoid(z[1])
where there's been implementation of the
这里面，它应用
sigmoid function that takes in the four elements of Z
sigmoid函数于Z的四个元素
and applies the sigmoid
也就相当于把sigmoid函数
function element wise to it
作用于z[1]
so just a recap we figured out
概括一下 我们发现
that z1 is equal to W 1 times the vector X plus the vector B1
Z[1] = W[1] × X + b[1]
and a 1 is sigmoid of(吴说的是乘以) z 1
而a[1] = sigmoid(z[1])
let's just copy this to the next slide and what we see is that
让我们把这些复制到下一个幻灯片 可以看到
for the first layer of the neural network given an input X
对于神经网络的第一层 给予一个输入X
we have that z1 is equal to w1 times X plus B 1
我们得出z[1] = W[1] × X + b[1]
and a 1is sigmoid of z1 and the dimensions of this are 4 by 1
而a[1] = sigmoid(Z1) 而它的维度是4×1
equals this is a 4 by 3 matrix times a 3 by 1 vector
等于 这是一个4×3的矩阵乘以1一个3×1的向量
plus a 4by 1 vector B and this is 4 by 1 same dimensions
加上一个4×1的向量b  这个同样是4×1的维度
and remember that we said X is equal to a 0
记得我们曾说过X是等于a[0]
right just like Y hat is also equal to a 2
就像y^等于a[2]
so if you want you can actually take this X and replace it with a 0
如果你确实想把X用a[0]代替
since a 0 is if you want as an alias for the vector of input futures X
因为a[0]可以作为输入特征x这个向量的别名
now through a similar derivation you can figure out
通过相似的衍生你会发现
that the representation for the next layer can also be written similarly
后一层的表示同样可以写成类似的形式
well what the output layer does is it has associated with it
而最后一层所做的事是与
so the parameters W 2 and B 2
参数W[2] b[2]相关
so W 2 in this case is going to be a 1 by 4 matrix
这样W[1]就是一个1×4的矩阵
and B 2 is just a real number as 1 by 1 and
而B[2]就是一个实数 即1×1（的矩阵）
so Z2 is going to be a real numbers right as a 1 by 1 matrix
所以Z[2]是一个实数 即一个1×1的矩阵
is going to be a 1 by 4 thing times a was 4 by 1 plus B2 is 1 by 1
这里就是一个 1×4的矩阵乘以一个4乘1的加上b[2] 1×1
and so this gives you just a real number
这最后得出了一个实数
and if you think of this last output unit
如果你把这最后的输出单元
as just being analogous to logistic regression
看作是逻辑回归的类似物
which had parameters W and b
它有着参数W和b
on W really plays analogous role to
W实际上是和
W 2 transpose or W 2's really W transpose and B is equal to B 2
W2相似，也就是W转置就是W[2] b则等于b[2]
right similar to you know
就像你所知道的
cover up the left of this network and ignore all that for now
把网络左边部分盖住 先忽略这些
then this is just this last output unit there's a lot like logistic regression
那么最后的输出单元就想逻辑回归一样
except that instead of writing the parameters as WMV
除了把参数W和B
we're writing them as W 2 and B 2 with dimensions one by four and one by one so
写成W[2] 和 b[2] 其维度分别为1×4和1×1
just a recap for logistic regression
归纳一下 对于逻辑回归
to implement the output or implement prediction
为了执行输出或者执行预测
you compute Z equals W transpose X plus B
你要计算Z = W转置 X + b
and a y hat equals a equals sigmoid of z
和 a y^ = a = sigmo(z)
when you have a neural network who have one hidden layer
当你有一个有一层隐含层的神经网络
what you need to implement to computers output is just the four equations
你需要去施行以得到输出的是这四个等式
and you can think of this as
且你可以把这看成是
a vectorized implementation of computing
一个向量化的计算过程
the output of first these four logistical regression units and hidden layer
计算出这四个逻辑回归单元和隐含层的结果
that's what this does
这就是这（两个等式）做的
and then this which is regression in the output layer
而这个输出层的回归结果
which is what this does
是这（两个等式做的）
I hope this description made sense
我希望这些描述易于理解
but takeaway is to compute the output of this neural network
但总的说来要想计算出输出
all you need is those four lines of code
你所需要的只是这四行代码
so now you've seen how given a single input feature vector at
现在 你已经讲过见过如何给出一个单独的输入特征向量
you can with four lines of code compute the outputs of this neural Network
你可以运用四行代码计算出这个神经网络的输出
um similar to what we did for logistic regression will also want to
类似的 我们对逻辑回归所做的一样也想
vectorize across multiple training examples
把整个训练样本都向量化
and we'll see that by stacking up training examples in different column in the matrix
我们会发现通过在矩阵的不同列堆积训练样本
or just slight modification to this
或者只是稍微的修改
you also similar to what you saw in which is regression
类似于在逻辑回归中看到的那样
be able to compute the output of this neural network not just on one example at a time
一次能够计算出不止一个样本的神经网络输出
but to your say your entire training set at a time
而是能一次性计算你的整个训练集
so let's see the details of that in the next video
让我们在下一期中了解这些细节